Po Ah Wong Junior Software Engineer

Mobile: 0415-167-868 | Email: opawong@yahoo.com | Website: oscarwong.info Github: www.github.com/PoAhWong | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/po-ah-wong

RECENT PROJECTS

VPath

A plan tracking and note taking app, Built with **React, Express, Node, REST APIS, PSQL.** <u>Check demo</u>

SLIMY

A SPA website that allows users to share their comments and ratings about movies. Built with AJAX, Node, Express, REST API and powered by OMDB API. Check demo

STELLA TIMESHEET

A website made for my partner to help her collect her teams availability to manage shifts. Now its been used widely by the chain restaurant she works in.

Built with **Ruby**, **Sinatra** and **PostgreSQL**. Check demo

Tic Tac Toe

A pure front-end web that can choose from two player mode and play verse an Al. Built with only **HTML, CSS, JS** and **JQUERY.** Check demo

EMPLOYMENT

Assistant Accountant

Australia Cenvic Construction

Mar 2018 to Nov 2021

Collaborated within a finance team of 3, with strong detail focusing and communication skills, well completed a large project in Footscray. Built up skillsets of results driven, detail oriented, customer service, teamwork, time management.

Assistant Accountant

Jack Gaddie and Associates

Aug 2017 to Feb 2018

Prepare tax returns for individuals, and prepare BAS and Audit for small business.

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A highly motivated Junoir Software Engineer with an Accounting background, who has built up strong problem solving, detail oriented and communication skills within past years working experiences, and well combined these skills into software development area.

SKILLS

- JavaScript, React, Node, Express, Jest Unit Test
- RESTful API
- HTML, CSS
- Ruby, Sinatra
- Python
- PostgreSQL

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

La Trobe University

Master of Accounting and Financial Management Mar 2014 - July 2016